harker.org 2019-06-30

# Privacy and Other Policies | The Harker School

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on February 22, 2018. 

The Harker School ("us," "we," or "our") operates [http://www.harker.org](http://www.harker.org/) (the "site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of the site. 

We use your personal information only for improving the site. By using the site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

### Information Collection And Use 

While using our site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address and phone number ("Personal Information"). 

### Log Data 

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser or email client sends whenever you visit our site or open an email ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, email client, browser version, device type, the pages of our site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, how you've interacted with our emails and other statistics. 

### Cookies 

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Like many sites, we use cookies to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site. 

### Security 

The security of your personal information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy 

The Harker School may update this privacy policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy on the site. You are advised to review this privacy policy periodically for any changes. 

## Other Policies

### Integrated Pest Management Plan & Policy

In accordance with state, The Harker School focuses on long-term prevention or suppression of pest problems through a combination of techniques and strategies that greatly reduce pest presence and the potential for pesticide exposure to students, teachers, and others at a schoolsite. For more information please read our Integrated Pest Management Plan.

### COPPA

The Harker School makes extensive use of online resources as part of its teaching and learning. This is done in a phased, developmentally appropriate way. Students receive individualized usernames, passwords and restricted email accounts beginning in grade 3. Our COPPA page outlines what Internet-based software vendors students access with their student user accounts.

## Contact Us 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at communications@harker.org.
